I am setting up losing today
HDFC Ergo has more than 2 lakh products
HDFC Ergo Optima Restore NSTSE
its monthly versus new launch so there are a lot of
requests for computers of both of these I am
sign in the video of the same Subah Prasad
Dwivedi I would like to tell you my name
is Goli A Quarter and I am a
certified financial planner and have it
play with which can make your
financial life easy and a happy Panchalite
compensation is also the topline of the leading company
creating benefits so this video is a
comparison of HDFC Ergo Optima
Restore HTC and HDFC Bank their mass care so
this is for those who are able to find out the side should take
access from both the companies which is better
which is good for them so
after its fashion you will get the charity which
you want to do which politics you want to do if you
want to see both these lines in detail you can see its link
in your description box Vishal's separate
front advocacy we go you in this
video  First of all, let's talk about the
eligibility criteria,
what is the eligibility criteria in both the policies, yes,
it is minimum entries for diet, interiors
and maximum entry, which is there in both,
entry for different sizes for children, this notification
maximum measure
prevent hospitalization means
bills before hospitalization and the balance after coming back from hospital, you
can get it done, the
expenses which are also there, then it is
60-day free, Advani's dress post is
sent in both, the restore benefit which is
if your base always ends
then restore gets triggered, that is the
same in both, now always and meat, if you have
SIM in both, you two spoons of dry ginger prevent
hospitalization and there is
no oil in the pan, it is graduated from
in both and see the promotion of Delhi
Cantt benefit on shadow combination, the
validity of the combination is for single room and if you
take the combination in schedule then the company
gives you some incentive, it also gives incentive
if your  There is continuous hospitalization for torn bones
and
these centers are provided on a per day basis. If we talk about restoration, if it is for
finalized and artificial legs, then
you get a benefit of Rs 800 per day,
maximum for telling that
if your policy is of 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50
lakh, then your maximum benefit will be ₹2000,
you can take ₹
800 in secure policies, maximum
800 above, those who take a secure policy, those who have
seen the security video, they
know, look at the super above, there is a secure
accept plan in which you get special fruit benefits for 3 years, if
you give cream, then
there
is thousand rupees per day and its maximum
limit is 1000, modern treatment in both the policies is
colored in it, in restoration and from 4 minutes
modern treatment is basically some robotic
surgery, it is still clear in some hospitals, there is
oral chemotherapy from robotic surgery, there is
stem cell therapy, so
all this is common, now always a day is very  The policy
terms are as per North Zone-2. The zones are
same in both the policies.
Delhi-NCR, Mumbai, Thane, Navi Mumbai, Mumbai
Suburban, Gujarat, Ahmedabad, so all these come under Zone-4.
In Zone-2, your premium is lower. So,
both have decided to take insurance cover in a preventive manner
according to your place of residence. Keep in
mind that if you do insurance cover for both, then
you are paying any separate amount for getting two insurance plans done. There is no such
payment now. There is no typing fee and there is
no payment for any kind of
renewal. Both have a lifetime guarantee. You
cannot refuse insurance till the time you are going to renew your policy. You can
remove the policy. A soft
glass cover is available in both the policies. In
case of critical illness of your plan, you can take it
back. Let's talk about the waiting period.
One of the two policies is the
initial waiting period of 30 days for post-
hospitalization.  You cannot do this
and emergency accident hospitalization
discovered from day one specific tuition
fees are waived like stone cutter
Rajdhani is half less there are some charges
this process is there are no constipation for 22 years
so both have a
specification waiting period of 2 years
so this is just waiting period if you already have any existing
problem you can take like share medicine for that you will have to wait for 3 years
in both the policies it will be a matter of what are
similar
in both the policies now where is the difference in both your practice matches
and that will be your deciding
factor what will be the first thing we will
talk to you about is time and what is there and Tiwari himself has a
time limit of 5 lakh to 15x and
in Tumer Secure there
is option from fault to breakdown and trouble so you can choose if
you want to understand this then you
can just look at other policies there was no limit in room rent
in Uppermars Store
but there are two types of policies in Optimus Secure  The
celebration has been done, if the policy is below fifty lakhs
then you can take single room, deluxe room and
rooms in which there is
no sweet category, you can take that and if the
policy is above fifty lakhs then there is
no typing on romance, there is premium
in premium restore, you know that you are in
this lab, there is a piece loop according to it,
then there are five one-side advices,
your ribbon is decided on it, here it will be 4
minutes ago best cream, that is, you prevent it
accordingly and how many members are there
in the policy, a film will be decided with it,
IAS member will not be SP office,
like and other proper plants,
if you take four cloves here, then 3532
payment will be there in the first four, then you will have a human
plate and the
premium of the secondary members of a family member will be
asked for the secondary members, but that total
premium calculation is done accordingly,
if you have taken the policy, you
can see it in the policy document, those who have
already taken it, they have the document mentioning how much
love and desire of each member and
wise  It happens that your next year will be changed
like Restore in which the fate will be decided, there will be a
change in premium collection from the back side that biscuits, coins and benefits
which are the main USP of such a plan, if
you have a coverage of suppose 10
lakh wards then from the first day you
automatically have a cover of two accident inches,
that benefit is not available in Restore, they will
talk about No Claim Bonus benefit,
job weather and players benefit also
which Restore already has, in which
you get 50% No Claim Bonus, Agra, they do
not take any claim in any year,
massage like if there will already be an active fan of 10 lakhs, then
its next twenty will be,
if there is any Maza, then the post will be
reduced, your last year
increase will be ready, in Secure it is
called Plus, it is respectful
Muslims, come, come, tea will give you your 50%
plus benefits, next left LIC
policy, you will have tiffin, its
mixture
2420 will remain intact - it will not happen even  This
claim has nothing to do with the job. The
limit for road ambulance is
₹2000 for hospitalization in Restore. There is
no limit in Secure. There will be a
limit for emergency air ambulance. The limit for hospitalization in the premises is ₹
2.5 lakh. The
limit for emergency ambulance is ₹5 for
hospitalization in Secure. This is available only in New Zealand. If
you are in a place where there are
no medical facilities, it
is necessary to take you to this place that you are
in such a condition that you can be transported
and there is an emergency, you
can click on Ram Balance. This is decided only in
India. The treatment is Ayurvedic, Unani,
Siddha, Homeopathy. Restore was not converted in
your Secure. That comment is
Friday and we must have seen that last year when the
soil has changed, many items in these
went into the valley like your bubbles,
disposable creation, so all this
information, wearing it, its cost is
quite high in clean. What would have happened earlier, then spotted
more, approximate in the game
₹2000 ₹3000 but now the department will
increase this cost 2233 had gone in this I will go
to Swayamvar for a week so for
that we brought insurance after last year in
which if you commit suicide
then non temple run symbol items will be yours so
here you have to take the idols
restored if you want that
in the box in your name but this possible items are powerful like that
when you talk about secure then it has
10 benefits and it is already
included that your loan tablet is SP so
you do not have to pay any extra separately now let's
talk about confidence this is the
size of the company you get the animal checkup so
what is its limit specified we will
talk about the restore if you have the file then
you can take one to two years but if it is high quality
then you can take everyone so finally
Bigg Boss has given the
maximum emphasis in the individual policy,
in this we will
talk about the forces in 2036  You will see
501 likes, 500 to
1000 2012 likes in classmates, you
can avail this, this is also a short
term plan, because two more things have been
added in this, apart from this table there is
time left of 1 crore or 2 crore,
so if you save time of 1 crore or 2 crore,
then you get
limited in play individual, it happens in 10 minutes, you
can get maximum appointment test up to thousand software,
so till here the benefit is in theft stop line, which is
if you turn on some points, that
means you remain active, turn on office points, then
you get 1000 points of mute, then
you get a like, so
premium, this benefit of is
not available in Secure, this
deductible option is a newly introduced
option, it was not available in Store, it
is available in Secure, that means if you want to
reduce your love
and you want that no one hates you  You
can also add your officers minimum. I like this
and deductible option. Just think about dowry.
If you want that the first claim that comes in the
morning is Sadbhavna Cricket Deductible, then
if you want a very
clean heart in the first claim, then the company gives you some
time in place of that, so you have to use polythene only this time, so
how is this,
if you take deductible and you have an
entry glass policy, you
get a discount of 25 percent, then
you get 50% light and sound on your premium,
that every year this rock, this verified
staff will get it, so keep in mind that
you cannot remove it before doing Bigg Boss,
if you have done the option on medical,
now in line you cannot remove it, you can
increase the time of
bramble, suppose 50,000 tweets, first you
can take one lakh rupees, but you
cannot remove it, so this juice is a
good option, if you want to reduce the premium, then it is
a good option, only then
keep an eye on it, flexible  If you want,
you can use the policy term. We will
talk about Polytechnic and
in our Mari Store, there are one year and two year
policies, that means you can take a front policy of Dosa.
In verification,
you can also take a one year, two year, three year policy. You
get some tips in Bigg Boss
scenes. If you pay 2 years premium
together, you get 7.5 lakh rupees
and if you pay
1.5 lakh rupees premium together, actually Kapil Mansour says, if you pay 1
year premium together, then the
temple sentence has an economic benefit debate on the
secure plan. If you are
going with the policy of Insaan, then you
can take the quality from Super in which till now the
cemetery becomes one. In this, you get more
benefits from what we are talking about, there is a
little extra coverage, you
can see that, so now we will talk about
what are the things different, so now let's talk about the
cost, due to which you will be
able to decide which plan you want to take, so
I am comparing  I am now for family
floater plan and I bought this cream
from Delhi, by the way I would like to tell you right now that
I am sitting in the tube, I will come once upon a time to
Gwalior, right now so I had come for some work, so
I am in this hotel room,
telling you the result of looted desire in the video, they are 35325 21 a here we
will talk and 10 lakh policy family floater
intellects if you have a total of 10 lakh
then your purse will be Mata 22-08-2017 all the
animals including CST
phase table 27, then for Noida the
premium is 62 years, if you also take this area
polish then 3209 save 1 year mark if you
take the Himalayas year polish together then
Sixty Thousand Words ₹2 secure etc
policy then the premium is 3308 for
tablets policy in this, which is the
deductible in them, I had just talked about, if you take a deductible of 50,000 then they will
drown you for free  I
take a policy of 2899 for 2 years of 10 lakhs, then
your premium is 193 without any premium and
2 years of
4600, so if you take an LIC policy, its
premium is 30
years and
if you take it for 10 years then it
works for you and now if you are
taking an LIC policy, the premium is 2835 for minors and the premium is
5200 for two years, so here if you
want to compare, you can also compare that
20 lakhs with the service potential of the
security because the security is
giving you the possession of the security from the very first day, so
you can get it back, that means it will be absolutely fine,
if you want to do less hard work, then
20 lakhs restore and oil your
secure, you can contact and see
which one is suitable for you, so
these were the couple of points from my side,
Optima restore and not whimsical, you can
ask anything, have any question,  If
I mix it then please tell me, I have tried
not to miss all the information, full of this
information so that you can decide on Sonata properly
and if you want to ask anything then
please tell me my phone number email id is
not mentioned and thank you so much for
watching my videos and a reminder if
you have read my channel till now then do
subscribe from Mirzapur railway
information will keep coming from time to time, we will meet
in the next video stay in the
morning we will talk about Someshwar options of
Delhi hospital
both this is a very beautiful video if you